HENRY CHEN

Ln. 435, Sec. 3, Heping E. Rd., Xinyi Dist., Taipei City M: +886952890993 holyman1010@gmail.com https://goo.gl/A6k0PL

Profile

User-centered product designer with over 10 years of experience in structuring, developing and implementing digital design strategies. Innovative use of technology and CRO to drive user experience and achieve business goal. Be good at coordinate cross-function to complete projects efficiently and satisfy customers with intuitive, user-friendly designs.

Areas of Expertise

- Conversion rate optimization
- Strong collaborative skills
- User interface design skills
- Front-end programming skills
- Project management
- User research and interview skills
- Digital marketing analytics and optimization
- Excellent problem-solving skills

Work Experience

Product Design Lead (4 direct reports)

AsiaYo.com - Taipei City, Taiwan

Apr 2017 - Present

- Develops, implements, and leading the company's design strategy.
- Transform high-level business strategies into a practical action plan.
- Utilizing monitor tools to conduct CRO and user experience optimization.

Sr.UI/UX Designer

May 2016 - April 2017

HongKu info Co.,Ltd - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Prioritizing project deliverables and assigning, reviewing, and approving work.
- Creating low/high fidelity prototypes and conducting user testing.
- Effectively develop UI in a clean, well structured, easily maintainable format.

User Experience Design Specialist

Oct 2014 - April 2016

SAP - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Served as UX consultant and created high-level wireframe, mockups and prototyping to communicate with related stakeholders.
- Guide and influence User-Centered Design Thinking methods and working process into diversity departments.
- Experienced in diverse projects(insurance, medical) and overcome technical issues.

UI/UX Design Lead

Jan 2014 - Sep 2014

PChome Online Inc. - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Primarily responsible for high-quality designs, graphics, mock-ups and layouts for new Web & Mobile applications.
- Designing, developing, and implementing new websites and landing pages.
- Collaborate with product management and engineering to define and implement innovative solutions for the product direction, visuals, and user experience.

Gameflier International Corporation - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Designing the website's visual imagery and ensuring it is in line with company branding policy or the requirements of the client.
- Designing graphics, animations, and postproduction digital photographs.
- Motion graphics design and production, After Effects, rendering, and animation.

Graphic Designer

Dec 2009 - Dec 2010

ShSpa Inc. - Taipei City, Taiwan

- Prepares final layout by marking and pasting up finished copy and art.
- Makes finished copy and artwork by operating typesetting, printing, and similar equipment; and purchasing from vendors.
- Illustrates concept by designing rough layout of art and copy regarding arrangement, size, type size and style, and related aesthetic ideas.

Education

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Department of Merchant Marine National Taiwan Ocean University - Keelung City, Taiwan

Technical skills

Research, Information Architecture, Wireframing, Mockups, Prototyping, Team Management, Conversion Optimization, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript